绿  色  房  间
靠
Shit.
山姆
Sam.
山姆  醒醒
Sam, wake up.
怎么啦
What's wrong?
靠
Fuck.
泰格  你怎么搞的
What'd you do, Tiger?
-啥时候睡过去的  -混蛋  你说呢
- When did we crash? - You tell us, asshole.
不知不觉就睡过去了
I guess I fell asleep.
嗯...
Yeah...
引擎都没关
with the engine running.
手机充满电了
Fully charged.
昨晚你打电话到没电?
Did you kill the battery too?
听到收音机里讲的吗
You hear the radio?
离这儿11英里远的地方有个室内溜冰场
There's a skating rink about 11 miles from here.
外面停车场很大
Big parking lot.
轮滑场还是溜冰场?
Ice skating or rollerskating?
只说他们还开放
Just says they're open.
咋啦
Why?
玩曲棍球风险更牛逼
Hockey players whoop more ass.
兄弟  这可不好说
I don't know, dude.
也见过不少轮滑玩得漂亮的
I've seen some pretty bad-ass roller skaters.
7点就去么
At 7:00 AM?
好吧  我也去
All right, I'll come with.
-山姆  -泰得
- Sam? - Tad.
太好了
Awesome.
我上夜班  但明天早餐时可以赶来见你们
Hey, I work nights, but I'll catch up with you guys for breakfast.
-好  -我的房间是楼上右转第二间
- Okay. - I'm in 2-R up the stairs.
凑合着过一晚  呃  车子停路边就好
Just crash wherever. Uh, park in the side lot.
后车门靠紧墙边  这样没人能偷车里东西
Rear doors tight to the walls so no one steals your shit.
就这么着
All right.
房里的所有东西都快长毛了
These all have mushrooms.
这小子是个好人
This dude's legit.
啥  就因为他下午5点起床
Why? 'Cause he wakes up at 5:00 in the morning
在头发里打上摩丝去上班么
to put jizz in his hair?
不  我是说他很实诚
No. He's true.
喂  呆鸟
Ree-Ree.
给谁电话呢
Who you callin'?
关你什么事
Is that your business?
手机账单可是我付
I get the bills.
我去睡觉了
I'm going to bed.
一起喝酒吧
We're gonna drink.
一  二  三  四  一  二  三  四
One, two, three, four, one, two, three, four ?
Legalize
Legalize ?
早上好
Mornin'.
你好
Hello.
你第一个睡过去的吗
You were the first to fall asleep?
好  我是来自华盛顿特区来的
Okay, I'm with the Ain't Rights
"非我权利"乐队成员
from Washington, D.C.
呃  严格说来  我们来自阿林顿
Uh, technically, we're from Arlington.
不错  不过这曲子是为"锡赛德动力"写的
Nice. Uh, and this is for Seaside HCFM.
不是电子杂志
Not for the zine?
那个我会另写一个版本
I'll do a print version for that,
要是你们没意见的话
but this will run on our college station.
这首曲子将在我们的大学电台播放
Uh, if that's cool.
好
Yeah.
说说看  你们乐队有没有出什么新东西
So, you guys working on anything new?
嗯  有几首新歌
Mm, yeah. A few songs.
大概够一张七英寸唱片的容量
Maybe enough for, like, a seven inch.
行啊  打算出版唱片吗
Sweet. Will you actually press one?
好说  能付起出版费就干
Yeah, if we can afford it.
哦  咋不  我认真研究了谱曲风格
Yeah, no, I really dig the analog style.
这让我意识到
Uh, which brings me to the fact
你们这样的乐队可是打着灯笼都难找啊
you guys are hard to find.
为何不在媒体露露面呢
Why no social media presence?
因为签下更多的演出
That's because booking more shows,
卖出更多的唱片  会坏事
selling more records would blow.
{\fad(500,500)\fs16\fn方正准圆_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\clip(50,154,52,273)\t(0,1000,1,\clip(52,154,335,275))\pos(238.2,237.8)}仅供学习  禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
请于下载后24小时内删除
这不是重摇滚
It's not hard rock.
没人想饿肚子做事  但是...
No one wants to starve, but...
过于现实和势利  将会失去...
when you take it all virtual, you lose...
{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\pos(57.12,210.56)\clip(134,195,134,227)\t(0,500,\clip(54,195,281,227))\fs16\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HECB000&\b1}翻译  校对 Luckydag
本质
the texture.
"本质"  什么意思
What do you mean "texture"?
{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\pos(57.12,210.56)\clip(134,195,134,227)\t(0,500,\clip(54,195,281,227))\fs16\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HECB000&\b1}时间轴  后期 Loriaef
你得身临其境才行
Just... you gotta be there.
音乐想要震撼人心
The music is for effect.
就得花时间  要侵入别人的思想...
It's time and aggression...
{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\pos(57.12,210.56)\clip(134,195,134,227)\t(0,500,\clip(54,195,281,227))\fs16\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HECB000&\b1}
严格上来说  要有盅惑人的魔力
Technical wizardry.
要与时俱进...
And it's shared live...
不然就完了
and then it's over.
灵感不在
The energy can't last.
Iggy Pop  伊基・波普
原始  颓废的摇滚的象征性歌手  音乐家
除非你是伊基・波普
Unless you're Iggy Pop.
他是不错  但我可不想
Yeah, well good for him, but I don't think I wanna
七十岁时还在听着小凶兆乐队的歌
be in my 70's still listening to Minor Threat.
泰格就爱听
But Tiger does.
我可活不过七十岁  所以...
I won't live to be 70, so...
好  好  依照我的惯例
Okay, so, uh, this is a good seg
细分音乐风格
into one of my traditions.
对你们每个人考量
Uh, for each of you,
我给你们起名叫荒岛乐园乐队
name your desert island band.
就一个可选?
Only one?
假如我称自己为"黑色安息日"
If I were to say Black Sabbath,
是不是可以得到奥齐和迪欧
would I get Ozzy and Dio?
没别的意思  就给你们乐队取个名而已
No caveats. Just name the band.
好
Okay.
错配乐队
Misfits.
不行  太糟
No, The Damned.
-嗯... -我去  错配乐队
- Um... - Oh, fuck it. Misfits.
-毒药想法  -克罗-马格
- Poison Idea. - Cro-Mags.
这名字不错
That's a good one also.
兄弟  你怎么不说点什么
Why don't you say something, dude?
斯迪利・丹怎么样
What about Steely Dan?
唔  不  蜡烛盒怎样
Hm. No, Candlebox
他是个肥佬
He's a juggalo.
-啊...呀... -小甜甜布兰妮
- Uh... uh... - Britney Spears?
喂...你...你会把这段对话
Hey... hey, you... you... you're gonna
-剪辑掉  对吧  -是会做些整理
-edit this, right? -I can chop it up a bit.
啊  原汁原味岂不更好
Oh, you should let it go raw, man.
什么时候上广播台
Um, when is this gonna air?
我们好做演出
Like, maybe we should plug the show?
这个  呃...
Yeah. Um...
我在纽约市政中心组织的最后一场演出
My last show at The Muni Center
结局不太好
didn't end well.
很多观众大吐口水  甚至扔秽物
Uh, lots of vomit, some fecal matter.
委员会知道了风声  暂扣了我的许可证
County commissioner got wind and pulled my permit.
但你们的演出我已排上日程
You guys were already en route.
不行  你得给我们议付费
No, you gotta give us a kill fee.
开了90英里赶过来
We went 90 miles out of our way.
有个后备乐队等着呢
I've got a backup lined up.
午餐送上门  费用减免50%
Um, lunch, 50% cut on the door,
包你们上头条
and you guys would headline.
还有什么说的
Is anyone still on the bill?
没了
No.
* I'm always broke *
* And I'm alone *
* I ask myself *
* What have I become *
* I must be drunk *
* I must be stoned *
* I ask myself *
* What have I become *
关掉那玩意
Turn that shit off.
我的分成也给你吧
I gave you my cut.
业主也要分  但我没...
Uh, the house got theirs, but I didn't...
分成四份  每人六美元
Split four ways, it's six bucks each.
6.87美元
$6.87.
6.88如果你...
.88 if you just round up...
你个屎蛋
You dip-shit,
赶时髦的朋克  狗娘养的小丑
fashion punk clown motherfucker.
-老天  -别乱来  柔道高人
- Christ. - Now easy there, jiu-jitsu.
可不想进监狱
Yeah. We don't wanna go to jail, too.
你刚把演出的事情搅黄了
I think you just ended this tour.
靠  别闹了
Fuck yes. Let's call it.
好吧  我们得抄近路回华盛顿特区
All right, so we'd have to beeline to DC.
现在油箱是满的
We have enough for one tank.
路上油不够  只有用虹吸管去偷了
We'd have to siphon the rest of the way.
不是问题
That's not a problem.
有米饭和豆类
We got rice and beans.
一路北上  保持时速80码
We can head up north. Take the 80 all the way.
老兄  你在做什么
What the fuck you doing, man?
打电话给我表哥
Let me call my cousin.
能给你们弄一场实在的演出
I can get you guys a solid gig.
哪儿  这附近吗
Where? Here?
就唱[场景已逝]
Scene is dead.
在靠近波特兰附近
You'd have to dip down closer to Portland.
该抢走那家伙收藏的黑胶唱片
I say we just gank his vinyl.
好啦  已安排妥当
All right, so all set.
明天日场
Uh, matinée tomorrow.
下午一点开门  你们三点赶到就行
Door's at 1:00, you guys are on at 3:00.
-我已经给过艾迪短信  -给多少钱
- I texted the addy. - How much?
350美元
Uh, $350.
净收
Minus your tab.
呃  事先说下
And, um, just so you know,
那地方是马丁靴  高帮鞋的天下
it's mostly boots and braces down there.
光头党  每场演出都有见到
Skins? There's some at every show.
啥  酗酒  毒品?
What? D.M.S.? Sharp?
右翼份子  严格来说  极左路线者
Uh, right-wing, or technically ultra-left,
但并没成组织
but not affiliated.
-你表哥还好吧  -好  好
- And your cousin's cool? - Yeah, yeah.
别谈政治  跟着丹尼尔
Uh, don't talk politics, but stick with Daniel.
我本想跟着去
I'd tag along,
但丹尼尔要带他女友来我这儿暂住
but he and his girl are coming here to crash.
买吸尘器之类的
Gotta vacuum and shit.
这么说那些人  不会是烧十字架
So they're not, like, burning crosses
之类的  对吧
or anything, right?
就是说  我们唱摇滚就好
Like, we just play rock?
演出一些早期的东西
Uh, I'd play your earlier stuff.
重金属之类
Heavier stuff.
一般我会保留原本
I usually keep the originals,
但这个还没画完...
but since this one never happened...
演出协议继续吗
Can I still run that interview?
好
Yeah.
哪个电台频道
What station is it on?
长波FM85.5
Uh, FM 85.5.
"跟冠军一起早餐"电台
Breakfast With Champions.
-多谢  -哟  法国小子...
- Thanks. - Yo, Tadpole...
差点灭了你  对不住啦
I'm sorry I almost obliterated you, man.
不碍事
Not a problem.
路上保重
Take it easy.
至少这小子画得不赖
At least the dude can draw.
真心不错
Yeah, it's pretty sweet.
哟  帕特...
Yo, Pat...
有件事  我从没跟人说过...
you know, there's something I've never told people...
这个事  谁都没讲过
or anyone, for that matter.
啥
What?
真是放屁声  咦呜
Was that real? Ew!
赶快开窗
Open your window.
好
Good.
你是泰得的朋友
You Tad's friends?
嗯  他让我们过来的
Uh, he sent us.
你是他的表哥丹吗
Are you Cousin Dan?
丹尼尔
Daniel.
你们看起来像醉酒刚醒
You guys look hammered.
在泰得家住一晚试试  保证你也这样
One night at Tad's will do that to you.
要是你女友想借住...
And if your girl's gonna be crashing...
别提这个
Don't mention that.
-好  我只是  -别多说  少操点心
- Okay, I was just... - Yeah, no worries whatsoever.
泰得  我和我女友之间的事
Just shut the fuck up about
不要提  明白
it him and me and her. Yeah.
流浪乐队  流浪乐队
Drummer? Drummer?
用我们的设备还是你们自带的
Using the house kit or are you using yours?
自带的就行
I'll use mine.
后台准备间在这边
Okay. Load in's here.
那话真恶心人
That's bullshit.
呵  "非我权利"
"Aren't Rights"? Yeah.
*  暗夜魔鬼  *
* Demon of dark *
*  黑天使  *
* Angel of black *
*  怨憎在燃烧  *
* Pure hatred burns *
*  大战一场吧  *
* Start your attack *
后台休息区里面走
Stage rest in here.
业主不怎么在乎防火规章
Don't block the hallway.
可别挡住走廊
The owner doesn't fuck around with the fire codes.
15分钟内做好调弦对音
Sound check in 15.
-20分钟后登台  -好的
-You're on in 20. - Got it.
*  暗夜帝王的奴役  *
* Darklord imperial slaves *
*  奴役  奴役  奴役  *
* Slaves, slaves, slaves *
嘿  泰格...
Hey, Tiger...
你还好吧
are you okay?
我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
开这乐场的人不会有什么古怪吧
Are these guys not creeps?
管理得滴水不漏
They run a tight ship.
不过却弄得像个幽闭的潜艇
Except it's a U-boat.
嗨  各位...我有个馊主意
Hey, y'all... I got a dumb idea.
刚说电源供应在哪儿来着
Where'd you say the power supply was?
看上去像个小型的变压器...
It's like a mini-transformer...
试音  一  二
Testing, testing one, two.
-喵  -收到
- Meow. - Got it!
有没联上
There's no guitar.
-吉他  -这该死的主意可是你出的
- Or not. - This was your fucking idea.
敢打退堂鼓  人们会叫你犹太佬
You back out now, I tell them you're Jewish.
上
Go.
晚上好  女士先生们
Evening, ladies and gentlemen.
我们是"非我权利"乐队
We are the Ain't Rights,
或称之"非尔权利"
or the Aren't Rights.
咋说都行...
Either one...
二  三  四
two, three, four!
朋克没有宗教敬畏  *
* Punk ain't no religious cult
朋克永远只想着自己  *
* Punk means thinking for yourself
别以为梳个鸡冠头就很硬核  *
* You ain't hardcore 'cause you spike your hair
自吹自擂其实没人看得上你  *
* When a jock still lives inside your head
纳粹朋克  纳粹朋克*
* Nazi punks, Nazi punks,
纳粹朋克  滚开*
* Nazi punks, fuck off!
纳粹朋克  纳粹朋克  *
*Nazi punks, Nazi punks,
纳粹朋克  滚开*
* Nazi punks, fuck off!
要是你想挑起打斗  不如早早离开  *
* If you've come to fight, get outta here
无事生非可不是好汉  *
* You ain't no better than the bouncers
扮警察不是目的  *
* We ain't trying to be police
蛮人做起了警察  天下岂不是乱糟糟  *
* When you ape the cops, it ain't anarchy
纳粹朋克  纳粹朋克*
* Nazi punks, Nazi punks,
纳粹朋克  滚开*
* Nazi punks, fuck off!
纳粹朋克  纳粹朋克*
* Nazi punks, Nazi punks,
纳粹朋克  滚开*
* Nazi punks, fuck off!
十个对付一个  可真有你的  *
* Ten guys jump one, what a man
打得越凶  警察就越开心  *
* You fight each other, the police state wins
敬我一尺  还你一丈  *
* Stab your backs when you trash our halls
有种就去抢银行啊  *
* Trash a bank if you've got real balls
以为纳粹十字标很酷对吧  *
* You still think swastikas look cool
真正的纳粹管教起小孩  你就笑不出了  *
* The real Nazis run your schools
教练  商人  警察  全都成了纳粹  *
* They're coaches, businessmen, and cops
第四帝国崛起  最先除掉你们这群人渣  *
* In a real fourth Reich, you'll be the first to go
纳粹朋克  纳粹朋克*
* Nazi punks, Nazi punks,
纳粹朋克  滚开*
* Nazi punks, fuck off!
纳粹朋克  纳粹朋克*
* Nazi punks, Nazi punks,
纳粹朋克  滚开*
* Nazi punks, fuck off!
用点脑子吧  *
* Don't you know you'll be the first to go
不然最先挂掉的就是你  *
* Unless you think?
滚蛋  快滚
Fuck off! Come on!
多谢  刚才只是开场
Thank you. That was a cover.
下一首
ould we do next?
花冠
Coronary.
这场免费
This one's a treat.
* Infiltration push reserves *
* Encircle the front lines *
* Supreme art of strategy *
* Playing on the minds *
不是说不管消防规范吗
What happened to fire code?
抱歉  伙计们
Yeah, sorry guys.
得给头牌乐队留点空间
We have to make room for the headliner.
奶牛捕手  对吧
Cowcatcher, right?
对  没你们什么事了  明白
Yes. You gotta clear out, okay?
钱给你
Here you are.
谢了
Thank you.
都在这儿  大家跟我来  好么
And it's all there. And you guys follow me, okay?
好的
All right.
再给你们几升油路上用
I'll get you one more two liter for the road.
快点
Okay, come on.
晚上赶路没事吧
You all right with that?
会小心  我明白
I'll be careful. I understand.
-啊  糟糕  我的手机... -什么
- Aw, shit. My phone... - What?
手机  我...会赶过来...
My phone. I... I'll catch up with...
-我帮你拿  -多谢
- I got you. - Thanks.
打扰了  各位
Excuse me, y'all.
啊  我靠
Oh shit.
-能报个警吗  -去你的
- Can you call the cops? - Fuck that.
喂  停下
Hey, stop!
怎么搞的
What the fuck?
说过别报警
I told you to follow.
不
No!
走  走  快走
Go, go, go!
啊  对  我...我想  说不好
Uh, yeah. I... I... I guess I am. I don't know.
有人...有人被刀扎死了
There's been a... there's been a stabbing!
她...喂  喂
She... Whoa! Whoa!
喂  喂  喂  喂  喂
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
见鬼
Goddamn it!
怎会不锁门  你没锁上门
They didn't lock the door. You didn't lock the door!
不  不要多说  别碰他们
No! Don't talk and don't touch them!
呆在这儿
Stay put!
不会有事的
It's fine.
-究竟怎么回事  -请给我一分钟
- What the fuck happened? - Just give me a minute!
事情很糟糕  看住他们
Something terrible. Stay with them.
-好啦  -啊  我去
- Okay. - Oh, shit!
没事  别担心  回房间里去
It's okay. Don't worry, don't worry.Get back inside.
这怎么一回事啊
What the fuck is going on?
上楼  回房间
Up. In the room.
喂  走  走啊
Hey! Go! Go!
快上楼去  没事  走吧
Up the stairs. It's okay. Let's go.
上去就行  快点
Just go. Come on, guys.
-靠  -没事的
- Shit. - It's okay.
兄弟  真该死
Oh, what the fuck, man?
没事  没啥事
It's okay. It's fine.
把广播系统关了
Turn that PA down.
-怎么没锁门  -你也在的
- You didn't lock the door. - You were right there!
-我后来不在  -安静
- Until I wasn't! - Quiet!
-你好  -这里是报警援助中心
- Hello? - This is emergency services.
刚被打断了  我上报一起刺伤案
Yeah, we got cut off. I was calling to report a stabbing.
好
Yes.
是  警官
Yes, ma'am.
有打电话给达西吗
Did you call Darcy?
他正赶过来  只知道关于...
He's on his way. He knows about that...
不是这事
not this.
哥们  不能把我们关在这里  你得放人
You can't keep us here, man. You gotta let us go.
没关你们啊
We're not keeping you.
只是留你们一下子
You're just staying.
-枪给你  -你这话什么意思
-You're up. What the fuck is that supposed to mean?
别紧张
Just relax!
各位  别紧张
Everyone, just relax.
警察正赶过来
Cops are coming.
-锁个门好简单  -狗娘养的
- See how easy that is? - Motherfucker!
-看看你做的好事  -安珀  别发疯
-Look what you did! -Amber, chill the fuck out!
好不好
Yes. Please.
-达西到了吗  -还没
- Darcy here? - Not yet.
需要支取600现金
I need $600 cash.
你刚支取了350美元
You just signed out $350.
人命关天
Somebody's dead.
账目还是要记的
Still gotta keep the books.
还需要什么
What else do you need?
一个忠实的手下
A true believer.
两个怎样
How 'bout two?
也许她没死
Maybe she's not dead.
说说而已
I'm just saying.
看看  没多少血呀
Like, there's not a lot of blood.
你明白的  有点那个
You know, so, like,
可能她只是...
maybe she's just...
又是谁说她...
and who are we to say that she's...
啊  我去
Oh, shit!
得了
Come on, man.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
搞什么呀你
The fuck, man?
血流出来了
There it is.
啊  我的天
Oh, my God.
放我们走  现在就要走
We gotta go. We gotta fucking go right now.
我们啥也没见到
Now we didn't see shit.
我们...都醉醺醺的
We... we... we were so drunk.
好啦  稍等下  行不
All right, just wait, okay?
警察正在路上
Cops are on the way.
小子们  上面靠边一点
Above and beyond, gentlemen.
想让我代劳吗
You need me to do it?
-不用  -又不是第一次干
- Nope. - Won't even be the first time.
赶紧
Hurry up.
刺
Go.
好  就这样
All right, that's it.
好了  我瞧瞧
Okay, let me see it.
刀子
The knife.
比管制刀具短一英寸
It's an inch too short for felony possession,
用不着担心...
so you don't have to worry about the...
说真的  把钱给我
Actually, give me that money back.
什么
What?
守住口风的担保
It's like vouchers and shit.
代为保管而已  快点
We'll hold it for you. Come on.
万一被拘捕  钱给双倍
If you do any time, we'll double it.
好好跟警察说
Now talk to 'em.
-你是受害者  -对  警官
- You the victim? - Yes, officer.
双膝跪地
Kneel down.
两个都跪地上  脚踝交叉
Both of you, ankles crossed.
业主来了
That's the owner.
我给过他电话
I called him too.
伙计们  给警官们空出地方做事
All right, let's give them some room to work, folks.
你是业主吗?
Are you the owner?
是的  警官
Yes, ma'am.
奶牛捕手  可以走啦
Cowcatcher, clear out.
喂  警察怎么还没来
Hey, where are the cops?
-拿齐东西  -我们怎么办
- Get your stuff, man. - What about us?
你在说什么
What are you doing?
安珀  正在商量办法  安心等等吧
We're sorting it out. Just hang tight, Amber.
你那一套挺不错
Your set was pretty good.
啥
What?
第二首歌  也就是后面唱的
What was the name
叫什么名字
of your second to last song?
呃...
Uh...
毒...毒物进化
To... Toxic Evolution.
哥们  唱得真艰难
It's fucking hard, man.
就像我对地上的妞做的事一样艰难
That's the one I did her to.
好  枪只有六颗子弹...
All right, he's got six bullets...
真要干吗
For real?
...要是我们一起上...
...if we all go at once...
-伙计们  打断一下  -做什么
- Guys, hold off a sec. - For what?
-我们几个什么都没干  -这不重要
- We haven't done anything! - It doesn't matter.
人们称之为枪弹
Okay. They're called cartridges.
再叽叽歪歪的话
The bullet is the part that enters your brain
枪弹的一部分  弹头将射入你的大脑
if you keep talking shit.
这支枪只有五发弹药  不是六发
And this gun only has five cartridges, not six,
枪弹个头过大  转轮只能装进五发
'cause they're big as fuck and only five fit the cylinder.
别考验我的耐性  都给我闭上鸟嘴
So, please shut the fuck up and don't test me.
里斯  别把事情弄得更糟
Reece, you're making it worse.
坐下  安静等待
We sit and we wait.
等死吗
And we die?
安静坐着等就不会
Not if you sit and you wait.
只有3点45分一个电话报警
It's just the one to 911 at 3:45
接着是我3点47分打的
and then mine was at 3:47.
你打过电话
You called?
-警局回电  我接的  -说清楚
- 911 called back and I answered. - Be clear.
除了在场的还有谁...
Who else knows besides...
你提起过丹尼尔的表弟
You said Daniel's cousin?
泰得
Tad.
昨晚我们这儿是有人发了个短信给他
There was a text from him last night with our address,
但泰得并不知情
but he doesn't know anything.
除了认识留在屋里的是谁  来自哪儿...
Except who they are, where they are...
更可能知道他们要去往那里
maybe where they're supposed to be next.
靠
Fuck.
查查邮件
Check emails.
昨晚他们可是当众演奏
They played their set to the crowd.
只能当是有人知道他们的行踪
Then we'll assume the wide world knows
并终将有人会找过来
and they'll be tracking that.
那个给我
Give it to me.
只是想争取些时间
I was trying to buy some time
控制局面直到...
and contain this until we could...
控制
Contain?
事态像野火一样蔓延开来
It was pretty rapid fire.
大家都喜欢乌姆  感激你挺身而出
I appreciate your initiative and we all love Werm.
他可是自家兄弟
He's a brother.
就算他进了监狱  你照样可以探访他啊
And you might have visited him in prison.
有分别嘛
Makes a difference.
现在局面搞得进退两难
Now we're all in the stew
就因为乌姆一时冲动
for an impulsive act,
不为他人着想的家伙
for a selfish act,
在我的屋檐下做出这种事
under my roof.
可有解决之道?
You see a way out of this?
对屋里那些人吗?
For them?
没
No.
还是得想个办法
We still have to find one.
好  还算好
Okay. This is good.
他们没带枪
No guns.
房子前面可立了"请勿擅闯"的牌子
You have a "No trespassing" sign posted at the residence?
写了"内有恶犬"
We got "Beware of dogs."
那敢情好
That's better.
有没有人知道我们上这儿来了
Does anyone even know we're in here?
-没有在乎咱们的人知道  -泰得呢
-No one who cares. -Tad?
-我们该走出去  -是该出去
- I think we go. - I think we go too.
下个敢乱动的人...
The next person that moves...
里面的人没事吧
Everyone okay?
就要有人倒霉了
Just about.
盖比
Gabe?
-对  开门  -不
- Yeah. Open up. - No!
-警察在哪儿  -好...
- Where are the cops? - Okay...
你是让我开门呢
do you want me to open the door,
还是开枪把你的脑袋轰掉
or do you want me to blow your fucking head off?
-给我退后  -怎么啦
- Back the fuck off! - What's going on?
他们想一轰而上
They're trying to run at me!
别对他们开枪
Do not shoot them!
这么说吧  这可得看他们的
You know what? That's on them.
警察在哪
Where are the cops?
把枪给他们
Give them the gun!
再说次
Say again?
事情结束了
It's over!
把枪给他们
Give them the gun.
可跟你说过他们想一轰而上...
Okay, I told you they just tried to run at me...
那就把子弹取出来
Then take the bullets out!
快把枪给他们
Just hand it over now!
别对他们开枪
Do not shoot them!
达西来了吗
Is Darcy here?
-来了  -我在
- He is. - I am.
里面各位  我是业主
Gentlemen, I'm the owner.
好吧  跟我直说不就行了
Okay, why the fuck didn't you just tell me?
这一切真的很抱歉
Truly sorry about this.
正在了解事情经过
Playing catch-up here myself.
这只是在做戏
They're playing a fucking show.
呃...
Uh...
谢谢你  但是...
thank you, but...
见到警察  我们才开门
we open the door for the police,
或者让我们保留子弹
or we keep the bullets.
对  是枪子弹
Uh, the cartridges.
没问题
I've got no problem with that.
好  枪给他们
Okay, I handed them the gun.
-我这就出门  -不行  不能走
-I'm gonna head out now. -No, you're not.
-让他开门走吧  -等等
- Let him open the door. - Hang on.
枪都给了我们  枪给了我们...
No, he gave us the gun, he gave us the gun...
没人可以...
Nobody is...
指挥做这做那  枪都给你们了  好不
letting me do anything. I gave you the goddamn gun, okay?
-该怎么办  -他说得对
- So how are we doing? - He's right.
帕特  心里盘算下
Pat, do the math.
-警察在哪儿  -还得多等会儿
- Where are the police? - It takes a while out here.
-退后  -在等警察的同时
- Stay back. - Just want to make sure that no one else gets hurt
不想让更多人受伤
in the meantime.
该死的  枪都给了你们...
Okay, I gave you the damn gun...
泰格
Tiger!
-把他弄倒  -贾斯汀
- Get him down! - Justin?
把他弄倒
Get him down!
怎么回事
What's happening?
嘘
Shh!
贾斯汀
Justin?
谁叫你锁门的  活该
Shouldn't have locked the door.
见鬼  山姆
Shit. Sam!
拿子弹
Get the bullets!
好好  快装子弹
All right, load the gun.
-里面究竟怎么回事  -没啥好事
- How's it going in there? - Not good!
好  但我们宁愿等警察
Fine, but we would rather wait for the police!
贾斯汀
Justin?
他没事...
He's fine...
但要他跟我们一起等
but he's gonna wait too!
明白了
Understood, gentlemen.
好好等着
Hold tight.
你觉得里面的人知道?
You think they know?
可比你聪明得多
I think they're smarter than you!
达西...
Darcy...
老兄
Man.
跟你道歉
I apologize.
只能这样干  封好路
We'll do it here. Stage it up the road. Okay.
哥们  这人好疯狂
Hey, what was that gonzo shit, man?
有次演唱赛中
So in a tournament,
有个家伙跟我狠狠地干了一架
I snap his arm
直到打折他的手臂  他才服输
or he taps out
双方都脸青鼻肿  像开了个紫酱铺
and we all go get burgers.
-打折他的手臂  -得了
- Snap it. - Come on.
你看  枪搞到手了
Look, we've got the gun.
为何不放过他...
Why don't we just let him...
等等  我可不想拿着枪
Wait, wait. I don't want it.
明白不  这感觉...很糟
All right? I don't... I don't feel good with it.
谁要
Who wants it?
-别给我  -哼
- Not me. - Hm?
-不  我没开过枪  -我行
- No. I can't shoot. - I can.
不行  不能给你
No, not you.
-那你自己留着吧  -山姆  先拿着
- Then fucking keep it. - Keep it, Sam.
我站起身后  再给我
I'll take it when I'm up.
当我放手时...
When I let go...
你会怎样
what are you gonna do?
操烂房间里每个人的屁眼
Butt-fuck everyone in the room.
给我像印度教徒一样坐好
You're gonna sit criss-cross applesauce.
说啊
Say it.
我会像个印度佬一样安静坐着...
I'm gonna sit criss-cross apple sau...
干得好
Nice.
靠在沙发上面
Now lean against the chair.
有没有另外一条路出去
Hey, is there another way out of here?
没
No.
今天可给它们喂过食
You fed 'em yet today?
无关紧要
It doesn't matter.
它们可是专干这个的
They're professionals.
也许到早晨会死掉一两只
You might lose a couple by morning
甚至整群死掉
Maybe a bunch.
如我所言  这些狗训练就是干这个的
Like I said, they're pros.
死掉也是理所当然
They earn.
会补偿你的损失的
You'll be compensated.
上帝  入场名单上有多少人
Christ. How many people are on that list?
良种犬1200美元
It's 1,200 for a prospect,
撕熊犬价格翻倍
two for a bait dog.
唯命是从  至死方休  雇人来干也行
No studs, no champs unless you wanna pay
2万美金一条命
20 grand a head.
克拉克  很可能会消耗掉一两只孽畜
This might cost you your livelihood, Clark.
只要用不着我的手下去做就好
As long as it doesn't cost me mine,
你的损失我买单
you're covered.
警察肯定会闻讯而至  把场子清理干净
There are gonna be cops, so clean up the residence.
别留任何蛛丝马迹
Maybe leave a roach in an ashtray.
让丹尼尔看守那扇门  把小货车开过来
Put Daniel on that door and bring the van around.
靠
Shit.
钥匙呢
The keys.
不清楚  肯定在里面某人身上
They're with them, I guess.
-应该是  -没钥匙不行
-I don't know. -We need them.
还有事要干
I got a ton of shit to do.
你先去
Go on.
这可是个大隐患
This is a fire hazard.
我可不愿让丹尼尔守那扇门
I wouldn't put Daniel on the door.
好说  大把人能干这事
Fine. Plenty to do.
丹尼尔去哪儿了
Where's Daniel?
他出去了  我在代他
He stepped out. I'm covering.
没什么事吧
Everything okay?
跟我在工具房碰头
Meet me at the utility shed.
买的新车?
This a new ride?
对
Yeah.
关掉引擎
Just turning it over.
会呛油的
I think it's getting choked.
过滤器出了毛病
Wrong filter.
-车子很不错  -啥事
- She's a beaut. - What's up?
给我找一帮打手
Need some of the squad.
红鞋带的才行
Red laces only.
-今晚么  -现在
- Tonight? - Now.
这是名单
The list.
名单上的人都知道这事
This is everybody who knows?
对  包括那些乐队
Yeah. Including the band.
知道什么
Knows what?
还在可控范围
Manageable.
从现在起  不要在名单上加任何一个名字
From here on out, not a single name gets added
红鞋带除外
unless they have red laces.
名单上可有80个人
There's 80 people in there.
再加上四个
You plus four.
车钥匙给盖比  以防要用到车子
Give Gabe the keys in case we have to play valet.
天就要黑了
We're losing light.
-能干得来么  -嗯
- You got it? - Yeah.
噢  小心
Whoa, watch out!
会有石棉掉下来
That could be asbestos.
-才没石棉  -你有手机  对吧
- It's not asbestos. - You don't have a phone, do you?
被搜走了
They took it.
-她的也是  -我要搜下她  成不
-Hers too. -I'm gonna search her, okay?
留神  那条可能是通着电的电源线
Careful. That one could be a live wire.
音响线而已
It's a speaker wire.
有什么发现
What'd you find?
呃...
Uh...
"Fleisch wolf"
"Fleisch Wolf"?
呃.."Fleisch"意思是...
Uh... fleisch means...
鲜肉
uh, flesh.
肉类
Or meat.
是个德国词  就像生肉沙拉里的Fleisch
Like a fleisch salad. It's German.
意思是"生食之狼"
So "Meat Wolf"?
对
Yeah.
这东西很牢靠
This shit's solid.
-哎  -她身上没啥东西
- Great. - There's nothing here.
把你的口袋掏干净
Okay. Empty out your pockets.
死基佬  过来搜我啊
Come search me, faggot.
一枪崩掉他
Just shoot him.
快
Come on.
能起身吗
Can I get up?
坐沙发上
On the chair.
慢点  慢一点
Slowly. Slowly.
口袋翻空
Turn 'em out.
哥们  另一个口袋
Come on, man. Other one.
我靠
Oh fuck.
好决定
Good call.
别惹毛我  都缴出来
Turn it out, for fuck's sake.
那是什么  快给我
What is that? Give that to me.
交过来
Hand it over!
哎哟
Oops.
等下  那可是个手机?
Wait, was that a phone?
噢  把枪指着...指着房门
Oh, shit. Point it... point it at the door.
枪对着房门
Point the gun at the door.
也许警察来了  突袭检查
Maybe it's the police. It's a raid.
-此话当真  -唏
- Are you serious? - Shh!
伊尔莎  退后
Fuck off, Ilsa!
你给我安静点  好么
Yo, quiet, okay?
贾斯汀  别乱动
Justin, don't move.
-枪指着... -谁都别乱动
- Point the gun... - Nobody move.
要不我们全躲后面...
Now if we get all behind...
都别说话
Nobody talk!
当心点
Careful now.
抽支烟
Smoke this.
行不
Deal.
要是这小初哥做啥你不开心的事...
And if the cherry does something that you don't like...
开枪就好
shoot.
安珀  多谢
Thank you, Amber.
管好自己
Get comfortable.
你个新纳粹  还挺聪明嘛
Pretty smart for a Nazi.
我可不是新纳粹
I'm not a Nazi.
你怎么卷进这桩事的
How do you fall for this shit?
就说给我造成伤害的不是白人
Let's just say the people who were gonna hurt me weren't white.
女人干的
Any of them women?
我的成长史蛮有问题
It's a problem where I grew up.
-各位  -今晚怎样
- Guys. - What about tonight?
-刚绑住了个纯种白人  -各位  嘘声
-I think we got a white people - Guys! Shh.
去你的
Oh, fuck you.
好象是主电源线刚短路啦
It looks like we tripped our main.
后备电源已经启动了
Our back-up gennie is fired up,
但今天只能到此为止
but we're gonna to have to
需要停业做些检修
call it a day and do some troubleshooting.
星期天再开放
We'll try again on Sunday.
门票免费
No door charge.
算啦  那天2点到4点饮料算我请
Hell, free drinks from 2:00 to 4:00.
在场各位打算参加星期三的"人种倡导研习"
Those of you attending the racial advocacy workshop on Wednesday,
要准时到场  除非另有通知
assume it's on unless you hear otherwise.
记住...
And remember...
这不仅仅是场聚会  更是场运动
this is a movement, not a party.
就这样
All right.
上天保佑  多保重
Stay safe! Godspeed.
有谁没分到烟吗
Who hasn't smoked yet?
好  大家随我来
All right, you guys are gonna come with me.
不担心他们会讲出去
You're not worried they'll talk?
他们懂得轻重
They've got priorities.
跟他们说假如能守口如瓶几天
Tell them the party is on
参加派对免费
us if they hole up for a couple of days.
先把事情压下去再说
Put this fire out first.
葛洛夫帮派呢?
Grove Street?
我已经吩咐供应毒品的手下
My dope nigger stamps in case
这几天压货不卖
one of these meat-heads
谨防这帮傻头傻脑的家伙因为藏毒罪被捕
gets booked for possession.
好
All right.
想办法找个安全的地方
Let's get y'all somewhere safe.
下面有宝藏?
Treasure?
地板下  意味着光明
Daylight. Underneath.
外面的人在动我们的装备
They're moving our gear.
-喂  -各位
- Yes? - Gentlemen?
现在就放你们出去
We're loading you out.
警察来了吗
Are there cops here?
事情有点复杂  警察来了又走了
They've come and gone. It got a little complicated.
真倒了大霉
We're so fucked.
呃  我嗓音有些嘶哑
Uh, I'm getting hoarse.
这个音量说话  你们能听清吗
Can you hear me if I speak at this volume?
-能  -能的
- Yeah. - Yes.
好
Good.
啊...
Um...
你们能一个人回答问题吗
and can we please elect just one voice?
好
Yes.
好  你们现在是困兽犹斗
Okay. Now, you're trapped.
这不是威胁  而是事实
That's not a threat. It's a fact.
哦  我们可有支装满子弹的枪
Well, we have a loaded gun.
这也是事实
That's also just a fact.
哦  我们手头的枪可多着呢
Oh, we have plenty more guns on hand.
只是想请你们离开
We just want you out.
不会伤害你们的
Not harmed.
听我说  你们手持的武器并未注册
Now, the firearm you have is not registered.
我只是想在当局赶到之前
I wanted it out of the picture
把那武器处理掉
before the authorities arrived,
但你们拒绝合作  所以事情走到了这一步
but you refused, so here we are.
-胡扯  -对
- Bullshit. - Yeah.
到了这一步
Here we are.
代我的手下跟你诚意道歉  他们慌了神
Oh, I do apologize for my associates. They panicked.
对  没错  老兄  我们...
Yeah, no shit! Man, we're...
听着  听着
Listen! Listen!
没人想掩盖事实
No one is trying to wipe the slate clean.
我不再关心你们看到了什么
Whatever you saw or did
或是做了什么
is no longer my concern.
想跟谁说  就跟谁说去
You tell whoever you want whatever you want.
只是想求得你的理解  关押你们在这儿
All I ask is that you understand you were held here
只是为了安全起见  事态平息自会放人
for your own safety before you were released.
好
Okay.
好  谢谢你
Yes. Thank you.
但事先...
But just...
事先说清楚...
just to be clear...
警察会回来吗
the police are coming back?
警察来了又走了
They've come and gone.
哦  老兄  这才是让我们担忧的
Well, that's what concerns us, man!
不过是想处理掉那把枪
I just want that gun out of the picture.
好
Okay.
-小心  -对不起
- Careful, man. - Sorry.
-我们该怎么办  -挖通该死的地板
- What do we do? - We dig through the fucking floor.
等在这儿行吗
While we just wait?
外面的人随时会开枪攻击我们
They could shoot us at any time.
是啊  但他们还没有
Yeah, but they haven't.
又怎么知道外面那些人有枪
How do we even know that they have guns?
毫无疑问  他们是有枪的
They have guns. No question.
怎么能信得过你?
We're gonna trust you?
-一点筹码都没有  -手机...
- We've got zero leverage. - Ask for a phone...
换枪
for the gun. All right.
他怎么办  -
What about him?
我是说  一旦我们开门
Yeah, I mean, the minute we give it up,
他跳起来袭击咋办
what if he just, like, attacks?
那就把他捆个结实
Then I'll wrap him up.
好
Okay.
就看外面的人怎么想啦
So we see what they think? Mmhmm.
好
All right.
我们给你枪  换个手机
Uh, we'll give you the gun for a cell phone.
抱歉  不行
Sorry, no.
好吧  那换把注册了的武器呢
Okay, well, how about a registered firearm?
好笑
Funny.
贾斯汀  你在里面活着吗
Justin, you alive and well?
-活得好好的  -好  那就好
- I'm alive. - Okay, good.
里面的各位  希望你们接受现实
Gentlemen, I hope you appreciate the situation.
毫无疑问  事情的确失控了
Things have gone south, no doubt.
要知道  假如不把枪缴出来
But you know if you don't hand over that gun,
结局可大大不妙
it won't end well.
你瞧..
You see...
就我所知  我...过来打理生意
for all I know, I... I come to my place of business
发现有外乡来的乐队
and there is an out of town band
反锁在房间里  手持未注册武器
locked in a room with an unregistered firearm.
-啊  得了  -而且里头还有人受伤
- Oh, come on! - And somebody's hurt inside there
甚至挟持人质
and maybe there's a hostage, too!
我还能怎么办
So what do I do?
是不是有权利干预呢
Am I within my rights to intervene?
是不是该踢开房门  直接开火呢
Should I kick down the door and start shooting?
还是...
Or...
把非法枪械从事态中撇开呢
can we just remove the guns from the equation?
这些是我的问题
These are my questions.
你们有30秒作答
You've got 30 seconds to answer.
好说  等等  请等等
Okay, hold on. Hold on.
谁有更好的主意吗
Great. Anyone got any smart ideas?
贾斯汀  趴在地板上
Justin, get on the floor.
TMD趴在地板上  快点
Get on the fuckin' floor right now. Go.
山姆  你过来
All right. Sam, come around here.
-慢点  从我手里接过枪  -好
- Slowly, I want you to take the gun from me. - Okay.
-拿稳啦  -是的
- You got it? - Got it.
轻松愉快
Okay. Nice and easy.
你合作  就不让你太难过
Play nice, and I'll be nice.
求你
Please.
别乱来
Don't do anything.
-这TMD太蠢的  -谁说不是呢
- This is fuckin' retarded. - No one's saying it isn't,
要么缴枪  要么举枪开火
but we either hand over the gun or we open fire with it.
-我选开火  -你没资格  懂吗
- I vote for that. - You don't have a vote, okay?
选哪条路都要冒大风险  所以...
I mean we're taking chances either way, so...
这么说死定了
So we're fuckin' dead, guys.
至少我发现  这样干
At least this way, we find out
大家支持的话  会争取些时间
if all we're doing now is buying time.
-对他们而言  -阿门
- For them. - Amen.
这个时候  我只是好奇
At this point, I'm just fucking curious.
好...给你枪
Okay... we'll give you the gun.
但我们会留着子弹
But we're gonna keep the ammo.
好说  为了所有人的安全起见
Fine. Safer for everyone.
一起搬动那该死的沙发
All right, let's move this fucking couch.
好
Okay.
好好  别乱动
All right, keep still.
退后
Okay, stand back!
枪会给你
You've got it.
来吧
Here we go.
可以上前吗
May I approach?
不行
No!
不行  我会扔过去
No. I'm gonna throw it.
小心  这枪可是别人送的礼物
Careful. It was a gift.
-外面的人想做掉我们  -别扔枪
- They're killing us! - Keep the gun!
TMD放开我
Get the fuck off of me!
喂  喂
Okay, okay!
喂  喂  喂  喂
Okay, okay, okay, okay!
去你的
Fuck you!
啊  我的天
Oh, my God!
别动  扎起来
Keep it up! Pull it up!
我靠
Oh fuck.
帮我一起移动那沙发
Yo, help me move the couch.
过来帮我
Help me move it!
糟糕
Oh, shit!
各位  事情很快会过去的
This will be over soon, gentlemen.
我要搞死你
I'll fuckin' crush you.
快抢开箱刀
Get the box cutter!
从他手中把开箱刀夺过来
Get the fucking box cutter out of his hand!
-晕过去了就跟我讲  -好
- Tell me when he's out! - Okay!
帕特  帕特
Pat! Pat!
看着我  看着我  看着我
Look at me, look at me, look at me.
嘘嘘  嘘嘘
Shush! Shush!
安静
Shush!
晕过去了  他晕过去了
He's out. He's out!
我靠
Oh, fuck.
压住伤口  快压住伤口
Put pressure on it! Put pressure!
我懂  我懂
I know, I know, I know.
深呼吸  深呼吸  深呼吸
Just breathe. Breathe. Breathe.
没晕
He's not out!
还没晕
明白啦
You got this?
要多久才会...
How long does it take...
直到确认...真的?
until we know... for sure?
搞什么...
What the...
啊  天呐
Oh, Jesus.
收起所有武器
Any and all firearms,
克拉克从现在开始接管这事
Clark will handle it from here on.
他有跟你说多久完事吗
He give you an E.T.A.?
你说不能带手机
You said no calls.
好  很好
Right. Good.
-手机也缴出来  -里头发生了什么
-Phones too. -What happened in there?
安排尼尔明天过来
Set Neal up for tomorrow
换上新的隔墙  粉刷地板
New drywall, pour a floor.
就跟他说漏水弄成这样
Tell him we had a leak.
-门框也得换过  -怎么回事
-Door with a frame, too. -What happened?
今晚发生了一起大骚动
Uh, a bit of a maelstrom tonight.
来访乐队伤了我们的人
Visiting band hurt one of ours.
谁
Who?
艾米莉
Emily.
也许还有大个贾斯汀
Maybe Big Justin, too.
那还干等着做什么
What the fuck are we doing then?
赶紧进去啊
Let's get in there.
各行各事可不行
We're not coming apart is what we are doing.
这事没处理完之前  少TMD的问问题
We're saving questions until this pig fuck is transferred off-site.
达西
Darcy.
最后机会  谁想撒泡尿赶紧去
Okay. Last chance if anyone needs to take a leak.
我弄丢了枪
I lost the gun.
换是我  坚持不了那么久
You held on longer than I would have.
嘿
Hey.
我要走出去
I'm going.
这儿没换气装置  没下水系统...
There's no air shaft, there's no sewer system...
啥都没有
no nothing.
看这儿
There it is.
现在什么时间
What time is it?
反正不是白天
It's not daylight.
有点进展就好
It's something.
让开路
Out the way.
哦  靠
Oh, fuck.
找找看哪里有门
Look for a door.
有发现通知我
Just let me know.
嘿...
Hey...
你朋友的事  真令人遗憾
I'm sorry about your friend.
靠
Shit!
让开
Okay, move.
我操
Fuck!
锁住了吗
Is there a lock?
也许外面上着锁
Other side, maybe.
白费时间
We're burning time.
等等  ...
Wait, but...
看  这有...换气槽
Look! There's... there's ventilation!
舱口才六英寸  好彩你上
Six inch ducts. Good luck.
再四处找找
Shouldn't we look around more?
都找过了
We just did!
上  上  上  用力推
Go. Go, go. Push.
海洛因
Heroin.
跟地上的她或我们都无关
It's not about her or us.
好大个的...地下暗仓
It's a... it's a big ass bunker.
-帮把手  -坑爹的死胡同
- Give me your hand. - Big ass dead end.
手给我  稳  稳  稳住
Give it to me. Hold it up, up, up.
好啦  别看  别看
All right. Look away, look away.
也许可以用地堡做点什么
Maybe we can use this to our advantage.
死定了
We're done.
不想再等
I'm done.
-明白吗  -想实践你的想法冲出去
-Okay? -You can close the door behind me
别忘记关好门
if you want to strategize.
还没准备好
We're not ready!
你以为外面那些人在忙些什么
What do you think they're doing out there?
怎么啦  大家都不清楚
That's just it. We don't know.
大家都清楚
We fucking know
一心想弄死我们
they mean us harm!
就不知道他们有没有枪
It's just that if have guns,
那为啥还没冲进来割掉我们脑袋
okay, why haven't they mowed us down already?
不能让我们无缘无故失踪
We can't just go missing.
他们想布置现场让我们的尸体被找到
They need us found.
好吧  随手拿点什么
All right. Grab some shit
准备夺路狂奔
and get ready to run.
冲出去找死
Then we die.
再等下去
Yeah, but the longer we wait,
肯定会死的
the surer that is.
泰格  准备好没
Tiger, you ready?
好  差不多了
Yeah, almost, man.
大家该不是认真的吧
We can't take it so seriously.
我们得...
We gotta...
把这看作是漆弹游戏
treat this like paintball.
啥
What?
瑞克・席尔瓦...
Rick Silva...
在溜冰场单身派对
helped organize the paintball
组织了一场漆弹枪比赛
for Skate-o's bachelor party.
打全场  我们少了几名队员
And we were short a few players to book the whole field,
于是人们安排我们队跟几个前陆战队员对赛
so they paired us up with these ex-Marines.
前几个回合
And the first few rounds,
那些前陆战队员把我们...
these guys just...
杀得落花流水
tore us to shreds.
我是说  对方无一中弹
I mean, zero casualties on their side.
而我一动不动卧倒在树后面躲藏
And I just cowered behind these trees
还是中了枪
till I got shot.
身上布满彩漆  但瑞克...
Covered in paint. But Rick...
泰格  弄完了没有
Tiger, you done?
好了
Okay.
帕特  你也别说啦
Pat, you're done, too.
兄弟  抱歉  我们得走了
I'm sorry, man. We gotta go.
没事
That's okay.
-这算是帮我们打气吗  -预备
- Was that a pep talk? - Ready?
也许不能每个人都活着冲出去  但...
Now we won't all live, but...
怎么说呢  至少不用大家都死掉
I don't know. Maybe we won't all die.
-给  -不用  我尽力跑就行
- Here. - No, I'm just gonna run.
好吧
I got it.
好啦  操他妹的  西蒙和加芬克尔
All right, fuck it. Simon and Garfunkel.
荒岛乐园
Desert island band.
普林斯
Prince.
我...
I, uh...
我还有点昏头昏脑
I'm still the Misfits.
老兄  振作点
True school, man.
一起出去?
Are we going?
对
Yeah.
麦当娜和...杀手乐队
Madonna and... Slayer.
来吧
Here we go.
当心
Watch it!
咋回事
What the fuck?
放我们离开不成
They're letting us out.
这场子有多少个出口
How many exits are there?
前大门  后门  大概厨房还有个门
Uh, the main, the back, maybe the kitchen.
-我总是... -窗户呢
-I always... -What about windows?
自个去找
See for yourselves.
靠
Fuck.
安静
Quiet.
见鬼
Oh, shit.
要不躲起来
Should we hide?
兄弟  爱怎么干是你的事
Uh, whatever you want, man.
我们...应该分头行事
We... we should split up.
完全同意
Totally.
他妈的
What the fuck?
泰格
Tiger!
啊  糟  糟了
Oh, shit, oh, shit.
糟糕
Shit.
不好
Oh, shit!
停手
Save it.
啊  我靠
Oh, shit.
咬  咬
Fass! Fass!
四处找找  咬
Voran! Fass!
咬
Fass!
嘿
Hey.
到处都是他们的人
They're everywhere!
里斯在哪儿
Where's Reece?
就剩下我们几个
It's us.
快  搬过去
Come on. Move.
山姆  你看
Sam, look.
生食之狼
Fleisch Wolf.
是首歌
It's a song.
意思是"绞肉机"
It means "Meat Grinder."
上  上
Up! Up!
真勇敢
So ist's brav.
这么快就不行啦
You're retiring him?
它精疲力尽了
He's worked up.
派哪一条狗去
Send in another.
派两条  了结这事
Send two. Finish it.
把场子里那回音系统搞掉
Kill that feedback first.
不然送两条狗进去
And if I send in two fight dogs,
里面的人会故伎重演
what do you think they'll do?
让我进去  了结他们
Send me in there. I'll finish up.
告诉我要注意什么
Just give me the rules.
好不
All right.
只能用刀
Blades only.
砍得稀烂就好
Sloppy is fine.
别深至见骨
Try not to hit the bone.
好
Okay.
带上乔纳森
Take Jonathan.
残暴二人组
Brute squad.
关好狗  我俩出来前别放出来
Keep him caged until we tag out.
还有气儿?
He breathing?
有点气  对
A little bit, yeah.
让他流血
Let him bleed.
死亡时间越晚越好
Later is better for time of death.
钥匙呢
Keys?
没
No.
他们进来了
They're coming.
我好怕
I can't do this.
退后
Get back!
不
No!
艾米莉在哪儿
Where's Emily?
你想做什么
What the fuck are you doing?
喂
Hey!
谁干的
Which one did it?
-乌姆干的  -胡扯
- Werm did it. - Bullshit.
谁干的
Which one?
他们怎么跟你说的
What did they tell you?
啥  想不想知道真相
What? You want to know?
想让他也知道吗
You want him to know?
知道什么
Know what?
乌姆发现她打算离去...
Werm found out that she was leaving...
但她没提及跟你一起走
but she didn't say that it was with you.
"绞肉机"
"Meat Grinder."
这首歌其实是他们给的绝杀令
That song was their cue.
你走吧
You should go.
来吧
Here we go.
花太久时间了
This is taking too long.
盖比
Gabe?
你没让丹尼尔看门
You didn't want Daniel on door duty.
咋啦
Why?
他和艾米莉的事...
Nothing concrete, he and...
没确凿证据...
and Emily...
一对鸳鸯鸟
Little lovebirds.
认出这个没有
Recognize this?
认不出
No, sir.
当然认不出  这帮小伙子累死累活
Of course not. You were still handing out
你只是站门口派派传单
leaflets when these boys made their bones.
去年复活节的事情
It's from last Easter.
地下乐队集会后  这东西本该消失的
Supposed to disappear after the boot party.
他一进去就讲个不停
He just started talking.
安珀还活着  说艾米莉是乌姆杀的
Amber's alive saying Werm did it.
不必在意
Never mind that.
你呀...
You...
乌姆救了我们所有人
Werm saved us all.
山姆
Sam?
没事
It's okay.
我是说  情形是不好
I mean, it's not okay.
-你也不知道  -他跟我们一伙
- You didn't know either? - He's with us.
不是那儿
Not where.
得分头出去
We gotta split.
我觉得这风道尺寸要大些
This has a wider duct, I think.
钻不进去的
We're not gonna fit through there.
啊
Oh!
丹尼尔  他能帮上忙
Daniel, um, he can help.
什么
Why?
他是谁
Who's he?
变节者
A traitor.
就算他们以前不知道  现在也明白了
If they don't already know, they know now.
我能带大家出去
I can get us out of here.
哇  阴谋调调
Wow. A conspiracy.
不对  千头万绪说不清
No, just a cluster-fuck.
这儿有匕首和砍刀  专门招待里面的客人
There is still blades and fangs for the visitors,
但时间有点紧迫
but we are getting lean on time.
万一要开枪  开一次就好
Now, if you have to shoot, shoot once.
不得不开几枪的话  那就连发
If more than once, keep it a tight grouping
因为你们得把尸体里的弹头挖出来
'cause you'll be digging the slugs out yourself.
至于丹尼尔和安珀  可以对他们...
As for Daniel and Amber, they can...
忘了什么来着
What did we forget?
从大门出去走任何一边都可以去到河边
There's a river on two sides.
反方向是个采石场
The quarry's on another.
我们可以沿着大道的方向走  找人帮忙
We can parallel the main road back, go for help.
好  那怎么出这扇大门
Well, how do we get past the door?
我了解很多你所不知道的事情
I know something you don't.
好  比如?
Good. What?
我知道那儿藏有...
I know where we keep...
手太慢
Too slow.
能走了吗
Should we go?
现在么
Now?
手头有枪啦
We have the gun.
应该行
I guess.
好
Yes.
Yes!
给我两发子弹
Give me two.
别乱来  不要对安珀开枪
Easy! Not her!
停火
Don't fire!
咬  咬
Fass! Fass!
咬
Fass!
快滚
Go!
山姆
Sam!
永远出不去的
We're never getting out.
靠
Fuck.
要知道  我还算走运
You know, I'm lucky.
还以为他们会对我开枪
I guessed at least they were gonna shoot me.
各位  三个外来者尸体就行
Three'll do, gentlemen.
第四个可以让他消失
The fourth can disappear.
是时候清理现场啦
It's time to start the clean-up.
需要个推帚才行
I'm gonna need a push broom.
这一切本该早就结束的
This is supposed to have happened already.
-是时候加把劲了  -好的  先生
- Time to sprint. - Yes, sir.
干得好
Well done.
该谢它才对
Thank him.
差点就从我  不  我们身边跑了
Nearly got away from me. Us.
不是该惊惶不安吗
Shouldn't we be panicking?
肚子有点饿
I'm hungry.
不想跟你死一块儿
I can't die here with you.
那就别死
So don't.
你懂的  有什么尽管...
You know, feel free just to...
你那个鼓动人心的故事  剩下部分跟我讲讲
Hey, I want the rest of your pep talk.
噢  没心情再讲
Oh, no. It no longer applies.
得了
Oh, come on.
好奇而已
I'm curious.
漆弹枪大战...
It was paintballing...
你躲在...
you were cowering...
对  瑞克・席尔瓦
Yeah, Rick Silva.
我们被这些伊拉克荣誉退伍军人
We were getting slaughtered
杀得落花流水
by these legit Iraq vets.
情理之中
It totally applies.
价值上千美元的漆弹枪  装满弹药
Full camo, thousand-dollar automatic paintball guns.
对手经历过真实战争
They knew real war
也是按真实战争的方式来玩的
and they played real war.
战术  军事手语  包抄
Tactics, hand signals, flanking.
把我们杀个一干二净
Just wiped us all out.
瑞克忍无可忍  他说"去他妈的"
So Rick gets fed up and says, "Fuck it."
不在意是否中枪
Didn't care about getting shot.
不在意寻找掩护
Didn't care about taking cover.
他真的是绝望透顶
It was hopeless, man.
最后一场  哨声响起时
So the last match, the whistle blows,
他直接冲了过去
and he just tears out there,
穿着截短裤  踩着胶底鞋...
full jackass, in...
像个傻蛋一般
in sneakers and cut-offs
把...对手整个队伍杀个精光
and he... wipes out their whole team.
一刻不停
Doesn't stop.
奔跑着  狂笑着  不停地射击...
Just keeps running and laughing and shooting...
直到对手全部中弹身亡
until they're all dead.
假装身亡吧
Pretend dead.
我俩现在面对的可是真枪
And we're up against real guns.
对
Yeah.
不管怎么说  真枪实弹我俩打不赢
Either way, we can't play real war.
那就假装好了
Let's pretend.
给你的
For you.
活该你干这些事
You already earned these.
烂摊子太难收拾的话  催催尼尔
Maybe push Neal, depending on the mess,
找个新的主场乐队
to start looking for a new house band.
要早点回归正轨才行
We've really gotta get back to a routine.
你觉得奶牛捕手乐队会讲出去吗
You think Cowcatcher's gonna talk?
更担心的是手下那些坏习惯
I'm more worried about their habits.
真该让他们远离毒贩才行
Really have to stay away from that nigger dope.
近来道上有批次等货在流传
There's a bad batch doing the rounds.
可以上路了
We're good to go.
准备完毕
We're set.
就当这些事情从未在眼前发生过
This all hinges on nothing having happened here.
你们可听清楚了
Now, let's be clear.
这一针会让它多活上一个钟头
This should keep him alive for another hour.
好心帮它个忙
I would consider it a personal favor
让这狗咬着别人的筋肉死去
if he dies with meat in his teeth.
来吧  来吧
Come on. Come on.
撕咬的命令是"法斯"
Bite command is "fass."
说这个词就行
It's all you'll need.
不计代价  里面剩下的人开枪干掉就行
Disregard. Just shoot who is left.
他们不计数在布置的现场内
They don't have to be accounted for.
不用操心犯罪现场鉴定的事情
Forensics is no longer a concern.
再拖下去  今晚的努力就泡汤了
We call this in late, all is for naught.
12号弹的霰弹枪  还有吗
You guys got any 12 gauge?
办公室没有  就去吧台找找
Not in the office. Try the bar.
-还剩下多少发子弹  -三发
- How many shots you have left? - Three.
还剩一发备用
So you have one extra.
没筒壳弹
No shells.
吧台后面  先去找找
Behind the bar. Better get started.
见鬼
Shit!
放松  放松
Easy! Easy!
别急
Easy!
别在这儿用鹿弹
No buckshot!
怎么回事
What's happening?
狗被吓着了  关掉这破玩意
Dog freaked. And turn this shit off!
试过  不是吧台那里的混音器发出的
I tried! It's not coming from our mixer.
你走  我们来处理
Go! We got this.
别告诉达西  或是克拉克
And don't tell Darcy. Or Clark.
-进去吗  -对
-We going? -Yeah.
嘿
Hey!
下来啊
Down there,
你这屎蛋赶时髦的朋克  狗娘养的小丑
you dip-shit fashion punk clown motherfuckers!
-转过身来  -猎头机器人
- Turn around! - Shazbot!
啥  什么...你说的是啥
What? What... Who is that?
奥丁亲自现身
Odin himself.
霰弹枪给我
Give me the shotgun.
不行  霰弹枪我拿着
No, I got the shotgun.
那你下这鬼地方去
Then you go down this fucking hole.
三发弹药
Three shots?
对
Yeah.
一听到两声枪响后
You hear me fire twice,
不管发生什么  冲下来找我
you come down no matter what.
-这是个圈套  -对  可不是嘛
- This is a trap. - Yeah, no shit.
要不你跟达西讲去
You wanna go tell Darcy?
他会气疯的
He's gonna be pissed.
看住后路
Watch my back.
去他娘的
Fuck this.
兄弟  快叫盖比
Get Gabe, man!
至少需要两个人在下面  一个守住上面
We need two down here and one up there.
九毫米手枪在谁手里
Who's got the nine?
我觉得在艾伦手里  不太确定...
I think Alan does, but I'm not sure-
啊  我靠  被挡住了
Oh, fuck! Block it!
帕特
Pat!
他就三发弹药
He's got three shots left!
婊子
Bitch.
盖比
Gabe!
安珀
Amber!
啥事
Yeah?
呃...
Uh...
算啦
never mind!
还剩两发
Two shots left!
试探得好
Nice fuckin' try!
操你自己吧
Go fuck yourself!
靠  靠
Shit. Shit.
呀  糟糕
Oh, shit!
帕特
Pat!
还剩一发
One shot left!
靠
Fuck.
没弹药
Zero.
啊  我靠
Oh, shit!
放开我
Get off of me!
搞定他了
Got him.
死透啦
Totally.
弄得这杂种死不瞑目
Flabbergasted that motherfucker.
假如我知晓事情会如此...
If I had any idea...
还有狗吗
Anymore dogs?
人呢
People?
没  没在这里
No. Not here.
他们...上路离开了
They're... up the road.
我不想进监狱
I don't want to go to jail.
有人知道怎么给汽车搭线吗
Does anyone know how to hotwire a car?
不
No.
算了  离开大路走更安全
I'd stay off the road anyway.
你要对我开枪吗
Are you gonna shoot me?
乌姆在哪儿
Where's Werm?
送他回家...
We sent him home...
走出林子前  别说话
Stay quiet till we're out.
前面是他家宅地
It's the residents.
他们在干什么
What are they doing?
你不会想亲眼目睹的
Something you don't want to see.
到达果园后  我们可以打电话报警
We can call the cops when we get to the orchard.
可曾亲眼见他们死去
Did you see them die?
有两个
Two.
第三个没见到
Not the third.
我要走上前去
I think I'm going.
你到了果园再叫警察吧
You can call the cops when you get there.
要是敢玩消失  我会找到你的
If you disappear, I'll find you.
会的
I will.
我发誓
I promise.
你应该跟他一起离开
You should go, too.
只是想增大胜面而已
Just hedge our bets.
你那枪里只剩三发子弹...
You got three rounds...
一只手怎么给霰弹枪上弹
and I've seen you pump a shotgun.
话很在理
Fair enough.
信得过他吗
Do you believe him?
嘘
Shh.
快吃
Nimm futter!
快吃  快点吃
Nimm futter! Nimm futter!
-我的天啊  -快吃
- Jesus. - Nimm futter!
应该够了
That ought to be enough.
别管  别管
Lass es! Lass es!
别管
Lass es!
做得好
So ist's brav.
走吧  走吧
Aus. Aus.
脚印抹掉
Wipe it down!
你认为他们会开着引擎吗
Do you think they'd leave the engine on?
对  直到耗尽油箱为止
Yeah. It'll run the gauge down too.
打电话给警察吧
Let's call this in.
快走  快走
Aus. Aus.
狗那边你搞得定吗
You got the dog?
我负责狗这边
I got the dog.
栓好狗
Tie him up.
枪给我
Give me your gun.
我没带枪
I don't have one.
不找支枪出来  我就喂你吃子弹
I'll shoot you either way if you don't hand me one.
扔掉
Throw it.
把现场做得像是我们的错
They're making it our fault.
这可是擅自闯入
You were trespassing.
在我眼里  这让人起疑心
It looks fishy to me.
用布料来封口
The cloth is to make it seal.
我可不会这么干
I wouldn't do it like that.
枪被他们缴了
They got my gun.
-闭嘴  -听着...
- Shut up. - Listen...
真要下手吗
So we're doing that?
不然过来干什么
Why else would we walk up here?
说不清  只是觉得...
I don't know. And I was gonna...
会毁了犯罪现场
ruin the crime scene.
哦
Oh.
不过是弄个新的犯罪现场罢了
I thought we'd leave a new one.
这一切...
This...
真是场噩梦
is a nightmare.
对我们来说何尝不是
For us all.
跟我说  此番话就是他的愚蠢遗言
Tell me those stupid fucking words are his last.
你可有手机
Do you have a phone?
真好笑
It's funny.
昨晚你听上去如此可怕
You were so scary at night.
我要打电话报警
We need the police.
好  我是来自华盛顿特区来的
Okay, I'm the Ain't Rights
"非我权利"乐队成员
from Washington, D.C.
呃  严格说来  我们来自阿林顿
Uh, technically, we're from Arlington.
不错  不过这曲子是为"锡赛德动力"写的
Nice. Uh, and this is for Seaside HCFM.
好说  能付起出版费就干
Yeah, if we can afford it.
哦  咋不  我认真研究了的谱曲风格
Yeah, no, I really dig the analogue style.
这让我意识到
Uh, which brings me to the fact
你们这样的乐队可是打着灯笼难找啊
that you guys are hard to find.
我想清楚怎么做了
I know what it is.
哪儿跟哪儿啊
What what is?
我心中的荒岛乐园队
My desert island band.
跟别人说吧  看他是否在乎
Tell somebody who gives a shit.